remington.com 2017-02-26

# Privacy Policies | Remington

**Effective Date: February 1, 2017**

  The [www.remington.com](http://www.remington.com/) website is operated by Remington Arms Company, LLC and its affiliates and subsidiaries (collectively,  “our”, “us”, or “we”). This Privacy Policy applies to [www.remington.com](http://www.remington.com/) and any other website offered by us, which references or links to this Privacy Policy (each a “Site” and together the “Sites”), and which may include our sites entered via tabs or portals accessible via Twitter®, Facebook® or other social sharing sites.  

Review this Privacy Policy from time to time as we may update or change this Privacy Policy at any time for any reason without prior notice to you. By using this Site, you indicate your assent to all of the terms of this Privacy Policy and its Terms of Use.  If you do not agree with any term of this Privacy Policy or the Terms of Use, do not use this Site or submit any Personal Information to us via the Site.

**Personal Information We Collect**  
We do not collect Personal Information unless you voluntarily provide it to us. “Personal Information” is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact a single person. If you wish to participate in some of the features and services the Site may offer, we may ask you to provide certain Personal Information. The Personal Information we collect may include your full name, phone number, date of birth, e-mail address, and mailing address. By initiating any activity or transaction that uses financial information on our Site, you consent to providing your financial information to our service providers processing the transaction to the extent required to provide the payment services to you.

**Cookies and Other Software**  
When you visit or interact with the Site, we, as well as our service providers may use assorted technologies that automatically or passively collect information about how the Site is accessed and used. This usage information may include, but is not limited to, information considered non-personally identifying such as browser type, device type used to access the Site (i.e., computer or mobile device), unique number assigned to identify such device, geographic location, click path taken through the Site, your use of features or applications on the Site, and other publicly available information. This information helps us improve our Site, products and services.  

We may use cookies, beacons, or other visit recognition software to improve the use and functionality of our Sites. A cookie is a small data file sent to your browser from a web server to be stored on your hard drive that may allow easier access the next time the same page is visited and to allow storage of items in your shopping cart between visits. We, or our vendors, may place cookies or similar files on your computer or other devices used to access the Site for security purposes, to facilitate Site navigation and to personalize your experience while visiting the Site. You can configure your browser to reject cookies by modifying your browser settings, but if your browser settings do not accept cookies from us, then some functions of the Sites may not operate as intended.

**Information We Receive from Third Parties**  
We may receive information about you, including Personal Information, from third parties, such as persons assisting us in administering or fulfilling a sweepstakes or contest. Also, if you are on another website and you opt-in to receive information from us, that website will forward to us your e-mail address and other information about you so that we may contact you as requested. We may also supplement the information we collect about you through the Site with outside records from third parties in order to enhance our ability to serve you. We may combine the information we receive from these third parties with information we collect through the Site.

**How We Use Your Information**  
We use Personal Information you provide for various purposes, including to provide products and services that you request; to assist us in distributing e-mails and to communicate with you; to administer surveys, polls, sweepstakes, contests, and other promotional events; and to do all things necessary to administer our Sites, products and services, and manage, protect and improve them.

We use the Site usage information we collect for various purposes, including to administer our Sites, products and services, and manage, protect and improve the use and functionality of our Sites.

We also share information as indicated below.  

**What We Share With Others**  
We may use or disclose your Personal Information and other information we collect to affiliates and subsidiaries, to third-party partners in certain joint promotional and marketing programs, to manage databases of customer information, to assist us in distributing emails, to manage the Site, to administer and fulfill sweepstakes and contests, in connection with surveys, or to take precautions against liability.  If you request products or services via a mobile device, your request will be transmitted to your mobile carrier’s network and your carrier may have access to it. Consult your carrier’s privacy policy for additional information.  

We may disclose information to outside companies that help us bring you the products and services we offer, and in connection with any services or products you purchase from us, to your credit card issuer, credit reporting and fraud checking agencies. We may employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include providing web site services, fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to Personal Information needed to perform their functions.

We reserve the right to transfer any information, including Personal Information, in the event all, or a portion, of our business or assets are sold or transferred, including in connection with a sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of assets, reorganization or liquidation of our business.

We reserve the right to disclose any Personal Information requested by law enforcement  or if we are required to do so by law, regulation, subpoena, court order, or by a government entity. We reserve the right to disclose any Personal Information to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements and to protect our rights, property, or safety and those of our users, and others.  

**Do Not Track Requests; Third Party Tracking**  
Unless your browser settings are configured to make your online activities and publicly available information about your online activities invisible to usage analytics tools, we do not presently have the capability to omit you from Site usage information we collect to the extent your browser only sends us a “do not track” message and does not otherwise screen you from tracking without any action on our part.  

Third parties, other than our vendors (such as our cookie server), do not have authorization from us to track which websites you visited prior and after visiting our website. That said, we cannot control third party tracking and there may be some third party tracking that occurs without our knowledge or consent.

**Third-Party Sites**  
This Site may link you to other sites on the Internet, which are not operated by us and not under our control, including sites operated by third parties that have merely licensed the right to use one of our brands, which sites we do not operate or control. You acknowledge that we are not responsible for the accuracy, or any other aspect of the content of sites we do not operate or control. Your accessing the links to any other sites is at your own risk and subject to the applicable privacy policies and terms and conditions of such websites.

**Updating Personal Information; Opt-Out**  
You can help us maintain the accuracy of your information by notifying us of any changes. If your Personal Information changes (such as physical or email address), contact us by email to [webmaster@remington.com](mailto:webmaster@remington.com) to update or correct such information.

  If you no longer wish to receive our promotional communications, each message will give you the option to “unsubscribe” from receiving further email communications from us at any time.  Your option not to receive promotional and marketing material will not preclude us from corresponding with you, by email or otherwise, regarding your existing or past business relationships with us (e.g., any purchase of our products or use of our services, or responses to requests for information you pose to us either through use of a Site or by other means), and will not preclude us from accessing and viewing your personal information in the course of maintaining and improving our Sites, products and services.

If you sign up to receive mobile messaging (e.g., SMS and MMS) offers and communications but later decide you no longer wish to receive them, simply follow the opt-out instructions included in the mobile message.  

**Children’s Privacy**  
The Sites are not intended for minors. We do not knowingly solicit or collect Personal Information from children under 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit your e-mail address or any other Personal Information to us through the Sites. If we learn that we have collected Personal Information of a child under 13 we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible.

We encourage parents to go online with their children. Parents should understand the sites their children are visiting and which sites are appropriate. There are parental control tools available such as browsers and filtering software that prevent children from accessing inappropriate sites.

**Your California Privacy Rights**  
Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California have the right to request from a business, with whom the California resident has an established business relationship, certain information with respect to the types of Personal Information the business shares with third parties for direct marketing purposes by such third party and the identities of the third parties with whom the business has shared such information in the immediately preceding calendar year. To access this information, write to Remington Arms Company, LLC, PO Box 700, Madison, NC 27025, Attention: CA Privacy Requests or email [webmaster@remington.com](mailto:webmaster@remington.com) with “CA Privacy Requests” in the subject line. Please note that, under the law, we are not required to respond to your request _**more than once in a calendar year,**_ nor are we required to respond to any requests that are not sent to the above-designated email or mailing address.

**Consent to Transfer Information to the United States**  
The Sites are intended for users residing in the United States and are governed by and operated in accordance with the laws of the United States.  We make no representation that the Sites are operated in accordance with the laws or regulations of, or governed by, any other nation.  If you are located outside of the United States, please be advised that any information (including Personal Information) you provide to us will be transferred to the United States and that by submitting information to the Sites, you explicitly consent to its transfer to the United States.

We do not intend to conduct business via the Sites with users located in the European Economic Area and Switzerland (the “European Area”), and do not knowingly solicit or accept Personal Information transferred from the European Area for any purposes. If you are located in the European Area, do not submit any Personal Information to the Sites. We expressly disclaim any liability in connection with any such transfer of Personal Information from the European Area.

**Public Forums**  
If you post self-identifying information or other content on or through public areas on our Site, e.g., chats, blog comments, this information is public information and is generally accessible to, and may be collected and used by, others and may result in unsolicited messages or other contact from others.  You are encouraged to exercise caution when posting online self-identifying information.  You warrant that you have permission to upload any third-party information and you agree to indemnify, defend and hold us and our agents harmless from and against any claim, liability, cost and expense arising in connection with your provision of that information.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**  
We may occasionally update this policy by posting an updated version of this Privacy Policy on our Site. All revisions will become effective on the date that the modified policy is posted on our Site.

**Contact Us**  
We welcome questions or comments on this Privacy Policy. Please contact us by writing to Remington Arms Company LLC, PO Box 700, Madison, NC 27025 or e-mail [webmaster@remington.com](mailto:webmaster@remington.com).
